hotgigs.com 2007-09-21

# HotGigs.com - The Staffing Exchange

## HotGigs.com

This website is operated by **HotGigs Inc. (HotGigs)**. Our address is:

**HotGigs**  
10729 Bren Road East   
Minnetonka, MN 55343   

You may reach us by email at [info@hotgigs.com](mailto:info@hotgigs.com) or call us at **952-697-2900**.

The terms "HotGigs," "we," "us," "our" and "ours" when used in this privacy statement represent HotGigs Inc. and its subsidiaries, divisions, branches, affiliates or companies under control of HotGigs.

The terms "you", "your" and "yours" when used in this privacy statement represent any user of this website. 

Important: By submitting personal data manually or in electronic form to us and/or by using our website you give your consent that all personal data that you submit may be processed by us in the manner and for the purposes described below.

**Scope of privacy statement  
**We are committed to the privacy and confidentiality of information provided by you to us. This privacy statement describes our current policies and practices with regard to personal data collected by us from you directly and/or through the website to the extent that such personal data is protected by applicable U.S. and/or European data protection laws. The term "personal data" refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, job description, health related data, birthday, email address or mailing address. 

**Notification of changes to this statement  
**We are continually improving our methods of communication and adding new functionality and features to this website and to our existing services. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law and the changing nature of technology, our data practices will change from time to time. If and when our data practices change, we will notify you of the changes via this page. We encourage you to check this page frequently. 

**Collection of personal data including email addresses  
**You may choose to buy products from us or receive additional information or services from us. When you purchase our products or request additional information, we request personal information about you such as your name, postal address, email address, telephone number and payment details. We may also ask for demographic information to enable us to provide a personalized service to you. The information you provide is either manually or electronically stored in our databases. We sometimes supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For instance, if inaccurate postal or ZIP codes are received, we may use third party software to fix them. 

**Use of personal data  
**We will use your personal data to fulfill your requests and we will ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes. Where we send you information for any purpose, it may be sent by email or post. When we ask you for personal data it may be used for the following purposes: 

  * We may contact you occasionally to inform you of new products and services we will be providing; 
  * We may send you regular updates on issues we think will be of interest to you; 
  * We may send you requested information on our products and services; 
  * We may use your personal data for marketing purposes and market research; 
  * We may use your personal data internally to administer this website and help us improve our services. 

**Unsubscribe  
**If you do not wish to receive emails from us and want to be removed from our electronic mailing list, please email us at the address given below with "Email Unsubscribe" in the subject heading. 

If you also wish to be removed from our post marketing database, please let us know by emailing us at the address given below with "Mail Unsubscribe" in the subject heading or writing to us at the address given below. 

**Anonymous data collected through this website  
**In addition to the information we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our website. For example, our web server automatically logs which pages of our website our visitors view, their IP addresses and which web browsers our visitors use. This technology does not identify you personally, it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our website. 

Our website contains hyperlinks to other pages on our website. We may use technology to track how often these links are used and which pages on our website our visitors choose to view. Again this technology does not identify you personally, it simply enables us to compile statistics about the use of these hyperlinks. 

**Cookies  
**In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use temporary "cookies" that remain in the cookies file of your browser until the browser is closed. 

Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information, which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not. 

We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as determining how many of our visitors are from outside of the US.

We may also perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from (i.e: aol.com, yourcompany.com) to more accurately gauge our users' demographics. 

**Disclosure of your personal data  
**We do not share, sell or distribute your personal data with unrelated third parties, except as otherwise provided for in this privacy policy and under these limited circumstances:

  * In order to provide you with the information or products which you have requested, personal data may occasionally be transferred or shared with other companies within our group of companies or third parties who act for us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. For example, sometimes a third party may have access to your personal data in order to support our information technology or to handle mailings on our behalf. 
  * We will keep your contact details on our database and may, from time to time, email or post you information to make you aware of our other similar products and services which may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive emails or post from us for these purposes, please let us know by following the "unsubscribe" procedure set out above. 
  * Where you have consented, we may also share your personal data with other companies within our group of companies or disclose your personal data to other businesses who may contact you about their products or services that may interest you. 
  * We may share, transfer or disclose the information in our databases and server logs to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, interacting with anti-fraud databases, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this website, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of our sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event. 
  * Where appropriate, before disclosing personal data to a third party, we contractually require the third party to take adequate precautions to protect that data and to comply with applicable law. 

**Data Access and Corrections  
**Upon receipt of your written request and enough information to permit us to identify your personal data, we will disclose to you the personal data we hold about you, for which we may make a small charge. We will also correct, amend or delete any personal data that is inaccurate and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes. You may update any information you have given to us by contacting us at the addresses given below. 

Requests to delete personal data are subject to any applicable legal and ethical reporting or document retention obligations imposed on us. 

**Links to other websites  
**This website may contain hyperlinks to websites that are not operated by us. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party websites or any association with their operators. We do not control these websites and are not responsible for their data or privacy practices. We urge you to review any privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal data about yourself. 

**Transfer of data abroad  
**If you are visiting this website from a country other than the country in which our servers are located (currently USA), the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this website and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data as set out in this privacy policy.

**Governing Law  
**This privacy statement forms part of our website terms of use and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Minnesota and the laws of the United States of America without regard to any conflict of laws provisions.

**Feedback  
**We welcome comments about this privacy statement. If you have any questions about this statement or any part of our service, contact us by sending an email to [info@hotgigs.com](mailto:info@hotgigs.com)

**HotGigs Inc.  
**10729 Bren Road East  
Minnetonka, MN 55343  
952-697-2900
